Out here at the 2026 NFL owners
meetings, I am joined by NFL Network
insider Ian Rapoport. And Ian, the
Vikings are on the clock when they hit
the the NFL draft at pick number 18.
What's an area of need you think they're
going to target? I I think what the
Vikings have done and you know, really
try to do this every year is set
themselves up to
uh really take the best
player available, right? I mean, what
you want to do in free agency is bolster
your roster, get to a point where you
don't need need anything, right? I mean,
they [music] obviously had needed a
little bit of quarterback sign. Kyler,
I'm sure will get to that in a second.
[music]
Um
you know, they had some players who I
think their status was a little up in
the air. The [music] main thing is
there's nothing that they have to reach
for, which is probably a pretty good
place for Rob Brzezinski and the rest of
the organization.
>> You did mention Kyler Murray, the
Vikings looking to make their
quarterback room more competitive. How
did you see that deal unfold and and
what do you think of the addition? I
mean, to me, no-brainer. And you know, I
think it's pretty obvious, people know
this, that if you're a quarterback who's
available, you want to get to Minnesota.
You want to work with Kevin O'Connell.
Um you want to work with Wes. I mean,
you that's that is where you want to be.
And I think when when Kyler's available
for an unbelievable price, basically the
minimum salary,
>> [music]
>> um Minnesota was where he wanted to get
to. And I think if you're the Vikings,
he makes a lot of sense, too. Right?
Like, I don't know what Kyler Murray
[music] is going to become. I know what
he has been
uh and to me, that is a franchise
quarterback. I don't know what he's
going to become. But you're going to see
it. And whatever happens on the field
will happen. It'll be fascinating
training camp. Someone will win the job
and someone will not. And it is possible
that Kyler Murray emerges out of this
giving the Vikings a really [music]
tough decision of do we let him go back
into free agency or do we try to keep
him make him ours? But if that's the
case, that means the season has gone
incredibly well and that's the best case
scenario. The Vikings are leaning on
interim GM or Rob Brzezinski, their
executive vice president of player
personnel. When you look at what he's
been able to do this off season, the the
free agency moves they've made, how have
you seen the Vikings, I guess you could
say, style
uh evolve under him? I mean, he's always
had a strong voice in the organization.
He's always been someone where you say
like if a team was smart and they wanted
to hire a GM who doesn't just scout,
doesn't just grind tape, but really
understands how an organization works,
really operates at a very high level,
does great contracts, makes really good
trades, just runs the business of
football, like he'd be someone teams
should hire. And for whatever reason, um
you know, partially because he's very
loyal, you know, Rob Brzezinski has
stayed in Minnesota, but to me, like
this is someone who probably should have
been a GM already. Wasn't surprised to
see him get the interim title. Um and I
would expect him to be a pretty strong
candidate for the full-time [music] job,
as well, as he should be.
>> And thank you so much. I know you got to
get back to your to your regular job,
but I really appreciate the time you
gave me. All right. Good hanging.